You're leaving, Peter?
You're going back to Manila?
Jin Ho, what happened to you?
It's nothing,
it's just work hazard.
Enjoy your coffee
because that'll be your last.
You're Kang Dae-Hyun.
[THUDS]
The cops already know
who I really am.
I knew it!
Berdugo, I think I saw Delgado.
Has your husband's body
been released?
Not yet.
It's not impossible
for the syndicate to have doubts
as long as they don't see
your body.
Then, let's bury Miguel.
I'm going to the wake.
Who died?
Didn't Joey tell you?
You're going to Delgado's wake?
- Yes, Hon.
- I'll come with you.
[OBB]
Boss, are you okay?
Oh, yes.
It's just my sister.
She told me something
but I feel like it's fake.
But everything's fine.
Are you sure?
Do you want us to stay with you?
[LIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's not enter the picture.
Boss Idol already has company.
Hi, Andrew.
Hi, Zoey.
How's mommy?
Well, it's still a waiting game.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You know, don't worry.
I already filed a leave
of absence from work
so I can stay with you.
Oh, that's perfect,
because Kyle, Elai,
and I have somewhere to go.
- We do?
- Yes.
That thing you had signed.
- Ah!
- Yes, I almost forgot.
Yes, there is,
that's right.
Oh, wait,
you're leaving me here?
Yes, don't you want
to watch over mommy?
I really have somewhere to go.
[♪CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING♪]
So, if it's okay,
can you stay with mommy?
Of course, yes!
Perfect.
Just tell me...
if you need anything,
and if something happens
to mommy.
I'll come back right away.
Yeah.
So, shall we?
Let's go.
Okay, okay, take care.
Bye.
[CURIOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Just help yourselves, okay?
[PHONE CHIMES]
Go ahead, help yourselves.
Here, get this too, okay?
Wait a moment.
Please excuse me.
Ma'am, Sir.
[♪UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING♪]
- My condolences.
Thank you.
I know I've said this before,
but I'm offering my condolences.
Thank you, Ma'am.
We just brought
a little something.
Oh, you shouldn't have,
but thank you very much.
We take care of other people.
Of course, we have to take care
of our own.
Thank you.
Why is it closed?
Because of what happened
to my husband,
we still can't bear
to see...
what happened to him.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll just prepare this.
Please sit down.
I'll help you.
- Okay.
- Let's start here.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
What brings you here?
What is this? A spot check?
Is Berdugo with you?
No.
Why are you looking for him?
Because I wasn't expecting you.
What do you need?
Where's your boyfriend?
That man needs
to explain himself.
I saw him being chased
by the cops.
If you're here
to report and blame him,
there's no need.
He told me everything,
so I told him to lay low.
So, you can leave now.
Let me show you these photos.
Probably, you have no idea.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Did he tell you
he was with a woman?
Ma'am, let me take care of this.
I can handle it.
Just sit down.
You take care of mommy,
and I value that.
So let me do this.
It's just a small thing.
Thank you so much, Ma'am.
You're really kind.
Sir Tomas is lucky to have you.
I'm lucky to have him too.
You know, even before we met,
he was already working with mom.
And you know how picky
mom is with people?
Oh, yes.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
I was nervous
when I first met her.
That's how mommy is.
But since she and Tomas
get along,
you know,
I know I can trust him.
Even if he's quiet and,
you know,
a bit aloof.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Bring out Jin Ho.
I need to confront him.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
If you want me to,
I'll finish him off too.
What, Liza?
Leave me alone!
I'm furious at that man!
Don't.
It's too soon.
We can still use
what we learned from him.
What's your plan?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir!
Don't open that, Sir.
Sorry.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hon, what happened?
I just wanted to look.
Why, Sir?
Sorry, Clarissa.
I was just curious about
what happened to your husband.
Hon, that's rude.
They don't want to show it,
right?
I feel so embarrassed.
I'm so sorry, Clarissa.
Sorry, too.
Curiosity got the best of me.
It's okay, Sir.
Don't worry about it.
No, it's not okay.
It's not okay.
I apologize.
We better go.
Let's go home.
Sorry again, Clarissa.
My wife is right.
I don't want to make it awkward
at your husband's wake,
so we'll go ahead.
If we can help you in any way,
just tell us, okay?
We'll go ahead.
Thank you, thank you both.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- I wonder who else came.
- That's right.
I feel like a lot of people
went there.
It's Joey.
Joey.
Elai, Kyle.
Our condolences.
Joey, my condolences
for your father's passing.
Thank you.
How did you know?
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
How else?
From our great reporter.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HEART POUNDING]
Come on, let's bring
this inside first.
- Yes, all right.
- I'll do it.
Boss, I'll take care of that.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Thank you.
Condolences?
You're not sure?
[LIGHT PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Because I'm sure there's really
no one to mourn for.
Hey!
You know we need to do this.
This way,
no one will ask about dad.
But thank you for coming
even though you know
this isn't real.
I want to know
what happened to you.
And actually,
I should have visited you
before.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Me too.
I think I should have exerted
more effort.
I mean, I should have
checked on you
because you're also going
through things with your family.
Honestly, I really
wanted to talk to you.
But of course, I didn't want
any trouble.
Trouble?
Why would you say that, Joey?
Well, of course, if Zoey
finds out I'm talking to you,
she might get mad at me.
Wait, there's nothing wrong
if we talk, right?
We're...
We're friends.
Of course.
I just mean,
if she sees me talking to you,
and she wants you two
to be okay,
or to get back together,
she might say I'm meddling
in between, right?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE REVVING]
Well, we're not together.
There's nothing between us.
But if...
we do become a couple,
of course,
I'd want to maintain...
the friendship we have, right?
Really?
Yes.
But I hope you don't believe
the rumors anymore.
Believe reliable sources like...
me.
Speaking of reliable sources...
I have a story for you.
It's not just from
a reliable source,
I actually confirmed it.
Okay, what is it?
Jin Ho, he's an enemy.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll tell you everything inside.
Even I was shocked.
Of course, we trusted him.
Okay.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I knew it.
My instincts were telling me...
there was something off
about that man.
That's why you had
a bad feeling about him.
And from the start,
you were irritated with him.
Then you always contradicted
each other.
Jin Ho?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
- Joey?
- Peter?
Joey! Joey!
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Sorry, I came right away
when I heard about
your father's wake.
Sorry I didn't...
I didn't comfort you right away.
Sorry.
Are you crying?
Of course, I'm sad for you.
You're smiling?
Are you angry at your father,
that's why you're smiling?
Should I tell him?
He is our friend.
I trust him.
Don't react, okay.
Miguel Delgado is still alive.
What?
- Watch your mouth.
- I said don't react.
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
So, you almost caught Berdugo,
the leader of the syndicate,
but he escaped?
[LIGHT PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes.
Then your father almost died
because Berdugo was hunting him.
That's why you pretended
he was dead.
Hush.
That's why there's a wake.
Then Jin Ho turned out to be
a member of
the Korean syndicate.
He wasn't really part
of the interpol.
And what? He only used us
to find his girlfriend?
Wow!
Information overload!
Hard to believe.
I thought that oppa
was my best friend.
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
So that's why...
you've got that oppa vibe now,
right?
I even thought you were Jin Ho.
Hello.
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
It's so hard being away
for a long time.
You don't get updated
about what's happening.
Sorry, okay?
I wasn't able to help you.
But that's fine.
Do you know why?
Because I'm here now.
- Yes.
- Even if it's just us three,
we're complete!
We're still a group.
- Yes.
- Right?
Complete!
Peter, Andrew, Joey.
What?
[PLEASANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on.
- Yes!
- Never say die.
Never say die.
Oh, Andrew.
Yvette.
Why are you here?
Who's watching mommy
at the hospital?
Zoey.
I just had to...
drop by the wake of Joey's dad,
before I go back
to the hospital.
Okay.
Well, we also went home
right away.
Because Tomas and I
had a discussion.
Discussion?
You mean you argued?
Just a little misunderstanding.
We'll be okay.
That's how we are
when we have disagreements.
You know, we just need space
from each other.
But we'll be okay.
Soon, he'll be back.
Uncle Andrew!
I knew it,
you were the one who arrived.
It's late.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Where's Kisses?
She's in her room.
Uncle, can you help me here?
[OMINOUS MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Okay.
It's all chill back home.
You know? Life is simple
in the province, quiet.
I even missed the noise.
Why don't you just stay here
again?
That's my plan, but I came
earlier than expected
because I thought Uncle Miguel
was gone so...
Sorry, you got worried.
What are you saying?
That's fine.
Well, I also intended
to learn from Jin Ho.
But it turns out he wasn't
a part of the interpol.
You know? I really wanted
to be a secret agent.
That's what I wanted.
It's so cool.
He really looked like
a secret agent.
But in the end,
he kept secrets from us.
Never mind, that's fine.
I'll still find a way
to achieve that.
Uncle Miguel! That's it!
- He's my idol now.
- Hush! You're so noisy.
Wait...
if the coffin is empty,
then where's your father?
Do you want to know?
- Where?
- Come.
Secret.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, Sir.
I'm just here, I'm not leaving.
Good.
Yes, partner.
Don't ever show yourself
to other people,
especially now, they might think
you're a ghost.
The one I want to haunt...
is Berdugo.
That's why we need to find him.
By the way, Cruz.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
That car I asked you to trace,
what's the update?
Nothing yet, they haven't
gotten back to me.
But if that car
belongs to Jin Ho,
most likely the name on
the registration is different.
Maybe even fake.
Okay, just follow it up
so we can confirm our suspicion
about Jin Ho,
that he's with Berdugo.
We'll take care of that,
Major Delgado.
Just stay put.
For now, let's focus...
on tomorrow's plan...
for your burial.
Ten-four, Chief.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
This looks old.
Did you get this
from the teddy bear?
Yes, Kisses found it.
Okay, wait.
We need a cable,
like the one for an SLR camera.
Let's see.
Hopefully, it works.
[OMINOUS MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[BLIPS]
[CLICKING]
[♪STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING♪]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Yes, speaking.
Mommy is awake?
[STIRRING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Mommy! Mommy!
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Uncle, can we come?
- Mommy! Mommy!
No, just stay with Kisses, okay?
Anyway, I'll work on this later,
okay?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll just go see grandmother.
- Andrew!
- Yes?
Is it true mommy is awake?
Yes.
That's what they said.
- I'm going now.
- I'll just change my clothes.
I'll go, come.
Don't worry, Uncle.
I'm not actually worried...
because we'll finally know
what really happened to mommy.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Mom...
[LIFE MONITOR BEEPING]
Mom...
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mom, we're here.
Doc, why is she like this?
I thought mommy was okay?
People coming out of coma
are usually like that,
awake but not yet able to talk.
Is there anything we could do,
Doc?
For now, nothing.
But to be honest,
this is a good sign
that she's on the road
to recovery.
But to be sure,
we need to run some tests.
Who can go to
the nurse's station
to sign some documents?
I will, Doc.
I'll also talk to Tomas
about what happened.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mom...
Mom, can you hear me?
Please squeeze my hand
if you do, Mom.
Mom, can you wake up now,
please?
I promise I'll be good.
Please.
Mom, just come back, please.
Mom, I really want to know
who did this to you.
[LIFE MONITOR BEEPING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Major Miguel Delgado was
a skilled and honest policeman.
He was the type of policeman
who will do everything
for service.
We want to thank everyone.
Send the evidence.
That's Eun Ji,
the owner of this gym.
Hopefully he answers us.
- Eman!
Can we take a picture?
Let's go, we're looking
for Jin Ho.